stickam.com 2012-12-09

# Privacy Policy

STICKAM™ PRIVACY POLICY

**Introduction**

When you register for a Stickam account, visit the Stickam website, or use the Stickam services (including the Stickam website) you share information with us. We have established this privacy policy to explain what information we collect, how we use and share that information, and how you can access and update that information. 

**Information We Collect**

Information Provided By You. When you register for a Stickam account, enter a Stickam contest or sweepstakes, or contact us by email, you provide us information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) including Contact Data (such as your name, and e-mail address); Demographic Data (such as your gender, age, location, and marital status); and Profile Data (such as your user name, interests, and material posted or transmitted by you that contains your Personal Information and likeness). 

Information Provided By Your Use of the Services. When you log in to your Stickam account or use the Stickam services (including the Stickam website), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit any website, including Device Data (such as your hardware model, operating system, web browser, unique device identifiers, and mobile network including your phone number); Traffic Data (such as when and how you used the Stickam services, who you interacted with, the IP address used by you when you log in, and the Flash IP address used by you when you Go Live); Location Data (such as information about your actual location obtained from your IP address); Cookies and Anonymous Identifiers (See Cookies and Local Shared Objects, Below). 

Cookies. When you visit the Stickam website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site, but can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our services may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Local Shared Objects. In certain situations where we use Flash to provide content such as live-streaming video and recorded video clips, we use local shared objects (commonly known as “Flash cookies”) to remember your settings, preferences and usage. Flash cookies are similar to browser cookies but are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your web browser. You may access your Adobe Flash management tools directly from the Global Storage Settings panel of the online Settings Manager at Adobe’s web site located here: [http://www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). 

**How We Use The Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect to provide, maintain, and improve the Stickam services, as well as to protect us and our users. 

We use Personal Information internally in order to promote and operate the Services and to introduce users to new features, areas or content. For example we may use Contact Data to send you information about our company, our products, or our services such as upcoming changes or improvements. We may also use Contact Data to send you promotional material from some of our partners and affiliates, or to contact you when necessary. 

We may use Demographic Data and Profile Data to customize and tailor your experience by displaying advertisements and content that we think you might be interested in. 

We use information from cookies and other technologies to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. In addition to our use of cookies, our advertisers may set and access cookies to collect information about people who view or interact with their advertisements on our site. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and judge their effectiveness. When showing you targeted ads, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories such as those based on race, religion, or sexual orientation. 

**How We Share The Information We Collect**

Information We Share With Outside Service Providers. We provide Personal Information to our affiliates other trusted businesses and individuals who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, data storage and security) related to our operation of the Services. Those contractors have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information as necessary to carry out their specific contractual obligations to us. 

Information You Share. Any Personal Information (including live-streaming video content) that you post or otherwise disclose on or through the Services (for example, in chat rooms, streamed live via your media player, or within your personal profile page) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name and other profile information (but not your email address) is displayed to other internet users when you submit content or send messages on or through the Services, and you can be contacted by other users who wish to send you comments. Any content that you submit on or through the Services (including any Personal Information contained therein) may be distributed through the internet and other media. Additionally, certain Personal Information from your Stickam profile will be pre-populated into your profile for social networking communities you join using your Stickam user name and password. 

Information We Share For Legal Purposes. We will share your Personal Information with companies, organization, or individuals outside of Stickam if we have a good faith believe that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; enforce the Stickam Terms of Service or other Stickam policies, including the investigation of potential violations; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of our company, our employees, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law; and to meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable government request. 

**Our Practices For Specific Features and Services**

We require opt-in consent for the sharing of Personal Information as part of the following features and services: 

Social Login. If you use Social Login to enter a chat session on Stickam, we will obtain and may collect Personal Information (such as your "real" name, email address, profile picture, names of friends, and other information you make publicly available) which you have provided to the third party social networking service (“SNS”) whose login credentials you are using, in accordance with the privacy settings you have set in your account with the applicable third party SNS. In order to determine what information may be shared with and collected by Stickam, you should review the privacy policy and other disclosures provided by the third party SNS whose login credentials you use to enter the chat session. You can prevent the collection of information you have provided to a third party SNS by creating and using a Stickam account to login and enter a chat session instead of using Social Login. 

Social Connect. If you use Social Connect to log into your Stickam account, we will obtain and may collect Personal Information (such as your "real" name, email address, profile picture, names of friends, and other information you make publicly available) which you have provided to the third party social networking service (“SNS”) whose login credentials you are using, in accordance with the privacy settings you have set in your account with the applicable third party SNS. In order to determine what information may be shared with and collected by Stickam, you should review the privacy policy and other disclosures provided by the third party SNS whose credentials you use to log into your Stickam account. Additionally, if you use Social Connect to login to Stickam, we may share your Traffic Data and Personal Information with the applicable third party SNS whose Credentials you used to login. You can control the collection and sharing of information you have provided to a third party SNS using the “user settings” or “privacy settings” associated with the applicable third party SNS. You can prevent the sharing of your information by Stickam with a third party SNS by logging in to your Stickam account, clicking on Social Connect in your profile page, and disconnecting the applicable third party SNS. 

Around Me. If you opt-in to use the Around Me feature of the Stickam website, your Stickam profile will appear to other Stickam members who have also opted-in to use the Around Me feature if they are located within a 150 mile radius of your location, based on the Location Data obtained from your IP address and the IP Address of the other users. We do not share your actual location. You can prevent the display of your profile to users of the Around Me feature if you do not opt-in to use the feature. You can control your Around Me feature settings by changing your privacy settings. To change your privacy settings go to http://www.stickam.com/member/settings/privacy.do. 

PayPerLive. PayPerLive provides users the ability to create their own social network communities using the Stickam Platform. When you register to become a member of another user’s social network community, you are providing Personal Information to us as well as to the user who created that community. Some social network communities allow you to sign up with your Stickam user name and password. If you use your Stickam user name and password to register with a social network community created by another user, Personal Information and Non-Personal Information will be provided to the user who created that social network community. We also share Contact Data with users with whom you have transacted business with (for example, when you purchase tickets to live events or subscriptions to premium content provided by Stickam users). 

E-mail Invitations. Stickam allows users to invite friends to join Stickam by sending invitations via an automated invitation system. We store the email addresses that users provide so that the respondents may be added to the users’ friend’s list. Recipients of invitations from a user may contact us to request the removal of their information from our database. 

**User Choice Regarding Collection, Use, and Distribution of Personal Information.**

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you will not be able to complete the account registration, or access and use those services that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from our affiliate companies, you may select the appropriate "opt-out" option. To “opt-out” log in to your account, go to “Settings” and click “no” next to the feature you wish to “opt-out” of. 

You may also control who receives Personal Information you post or otherwise disclose. To control who receives your Personal Information, log in to your account, click on “Go Live” and set your Privacy Settings. You may have to change your Privacy Settings each time you go live if you have disabled the ability to use Flash Cookies in the Global Storage Settings panel of the Adobe online Settings Manager as discussed above. 

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

We will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers, and we take reasonable measures to protect such information from disclosure to or access by third parties. Please note that we do not guarantee the security of user account information or Personal Information, and there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the internet will be intercepted. 

**User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information.**

You are solely responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personal Information or other account information you submit. Inaccurate information will affect the services you receive when using our Services as well as our ability to contact you. 

We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may visit your personal profile in order to: (a) review and update your Personal Information; (b) choose whether or not you wish to receive promotional material from us. 

**Lost or Stolen Information**

You must promptly notify us if your user name, or password is or you have cause to believe has been lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that user name, and/or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

**Links and Public Information**

For your convenience, the Services may contain links directing you to other third-party websites. We do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you choose to be linked to third-party websites, you should review the Privacy Policy posted on this other website in order to understand how the third-party collects and uses your Personal Information. 

Please understand that any information that is disclosed in chat rooms, forums, message boards and other public areas becomes public information. We have no control over the use of such information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information on these areas. Further, it is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever links you select or software you download is free of such items as viruses, worms, Trojan horses, date or time bombs and other items of a destructive nature. 

**Notice Concerning Children**

You must be at least 14 years of age to register for a Stickam account and use the Stickam services. We do not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13, nor do we direct any content specifically at children under the age of 13. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user is underage, we will promptly delete any Personal Information in that user’s account(s). 

**California Privacy Rights**

California residents can ask companies with whom they have an established business relationship to provide (a) a list of the categories of Personal Information that a business has disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes for the immediately preceding calendar year, and (b) the names and addresses of such third parties. To request this information from us, please email us at [support@stickam.com](mailto:support@stickam.com); or write us at 444 S. Flower Street, Suite 3000, Los Angeles, California 90071. We will respond to such properly addressed written requests. Please note that we are only required to respond to each customer once per calendar year. 

**International Users**

The Services are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you access the Services from any region or country with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States law, please be advised that through your continued use of the Services, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States, and you consent to that transfer. 

**Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting. 

Revised: July 7, 2012
